<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resumes on Ivo Camargo - Web Developer and Game Developer</title>
    <link>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resumes on Ivo Camargo - Web Developer and Game Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Full Web Developer and Game Developer (Full time and Freelance)</title>
      <link>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/1-fulltime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/1-fulltime/</guid>
      <description>Freelancing using various web technologies. Maintenance of web systems and private servers for online multiplayer games. Development of web systems and games in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Developer and Full Stack Web Developer (Full-Time)</title>
      <link>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/5-blazebet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/5-blazebet/</guid>
      <description> DISCLAIMER: The &#34;company&#34; did not compensate its employees, and we experienced non-payment, bad faith and scam from them, so I decided to make my part of the project open-source. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junior Game Developer and Front-End Developer (Full-Time)</title>
      <link>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/2-igs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/2-igs/</guid>
      <description>Development of casino and videobingo web games produced for Ortiz Gaming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT Game Developer and Full Stack Web Developer (Freelance)</title>
      <link>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/3-oni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/3-oni/</guid>
      <description>Oni Mansion is an online multiplayer NFT casual game where players can decorate their homes with spooky decorations and haunt each other&amp;rsquo;s houses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFT Game Developer and Full Stack Web Developer (Full-Time)</title>
      <link>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/4-solport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivopc.github.io/en/resume/4-solport/</guid>
      <description>Solstead Surreal World is a Web-based NFT social multiplayer online game with gameplay similar to Club Penguin, where the player has an NFT character and can purchase NFT land within a metaverse.&#xA;Note: The Solstead Surreal World that I developed has been archived, and its foundation was reused to create Solstead Arcade games. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
